{
    "subject": "resource/Yours_Fatally",
    "predicate": "property/artist",
    "object": "resource/Big_Brovaz",
    "human_readable": "The artist behind Yours Fatally is Big Brovaz.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7257254123687744,
            "question": "What is the name of the artist behind 'Yours Fatally'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5084686875343323,
            "question": "Can you describe the musical style of Big Brovaz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42526140809059143,
            "question": "Is Big Brovaz known for creating music in a particular genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4204503297805786,
            "question": "Are there any other popular songs by Big Brovaz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4180270731449127,
            "question": "Who created the song 'Yours Fatally'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2735338807106018,
            "question": "Which musical group is responsible for the song 'Yours Fatally'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26209428906440735,
            "question": "When was 'Yours Fatally' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21174241602420807,
            "question": "Has 'Yours Fatally' been featured in any movies or TV shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20911796391010284,
            "question": "What is the general theme or mood of the song 'Yours Fatally'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19063463807106018,
            "question": "What impact did 'Yours Fatally' have on popular music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The artist behind Yours Fatally is Big Brovaz.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1425_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the general theme or mood of the song 'Yours Fatally'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1425_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has 'Yours Fatally' been featured in any movies or TV shows?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1425_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'Yours Fatally' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1425_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1425_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1425_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1425_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1425_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1425_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1425_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1425_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1425_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1425_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1425_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents mention \"Yours Fatally\" as a song by Big Brovaz, and provide information about the group's discography, including \"Yours Fatally\" as one of their songs. Therefore, the triple stating that the artist behind \"Yours Fatally\" is Big Brovaz is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information mentions the song \"Yours Fatally\" and attributes it to the group Big Brovaz, supporting the statement that \"The artist behind 'Yours Fatally' is Big Brovaz.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}